Priyanka Basak

• E-mail: basakpriyanka46@gmail.com, Tel: +91-8918510618 • Bangalore, India

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a multi-disciplinary professional with almost 3 years of formal work experience in Operations, Finance and Quality Management System and Process Excellence. Recently dabbled with the Food and Beverages industry, by attempting to start my very own Cloud Kitchen business

EXPERIENCE

The Cloud Co-founder

Jan 2022-Dec 2022

- B2B Marketing and Market Research To fuel our B2B business, we conducted menu evaluations, quality testing, focus group discussions with 3rd party consultants in order to arrive at a desirable selection of items at market favourable cost.
- Digital Marketing Ran Facebook and Instagram ad campaigns and also undertook marketing and taking orders via Whatsapp Business. Created content and chose applicable demography for digital/social media reach-outs. I also created our company logo keeping in mind what our Brand would want to represent (Bong Foods representing Bengali Culture and our universal love for Good food!!!)
- HR I led the hiring processes for our chefs, admins. Conducted thorough evaluations on LinkedIn, OLX, Work India, etc. and discussed salaries. Post hiring, I conducted taste tests with new Chef.

Tata Medical Centre Kolkata <u>Co-Ordinator in out-patient department</u>

Apr 2021-Dec 2021

- 100% on time communication with patients about their status and condition through emails, phone and face-to-face conversations
- Reduced TAT of Fast-track service for OPD patient to minimize their waiting time to improve the patient care services and Managed patient accounts with contact information, Verified insurance and financial information in a confidential manner
- Conceptualized and developed separate spreadsheet for doctor in-time, Patient waiting time and daily wise numbers OPD patients

Fortis Hospital Anandapur Kolkata Supervisor in Financial Department

Mar 2019-Mar 2021

- Analysed costs, pricing, variable contributions, sales results and the company's actual performance and took responsible
 for making deduction analysis report on TPA and corporate patients over a monthly budget and reconciled overall daily
 monthly and yearly transactions.
- Created effective packages including pre, intra and post operative services. Responsible for making Doctors agreement.
- Conducted review of financial statements by carrying out audits to evaluate revenues and expenditure and Created a key dashboard for monitoring OT.

EDUCATION

College of Paramedical and Allied Health Sciences and JNM Govt. Medical College and Hospital of West Bengal University of Health Sciences

Masters in Hospital Administration

Jan 2020 – Till Present

- 61 rank in WBMAT entrance among 10 lakh candidates
- 2nd semester Operation and Research Methodology paper got 95% and topper in university
- Class representative in our batch

Peerless Hospital & B.K.Roy Research Centre of Maulana Abul Kalam Azad University of Technology (formerly known as WBUT) with 6.34 DGPA.

Bachelor of Hospital Management

Aug 2016- May 2019

- Got awarded excellence certificate for my final semester Thesis titled "Introducing Disaster Management in Govt. Hospital"
- Awarded 1st position for dance and fashion shows in college cultural programme